{
    "id": "7080979747cb4507aa83b1e2d6ad59eb",
    "title": "Tenses Exercise (Passive Forms)",
    "exercises": [
        {
            "id": "5ad36717ba8c4aeca4235a8206103fe6",
            "title": "Tenses Exercise (Passive Voice)",
            "questions": [
                {
                    "question": "The prizes ……………………………… away by the chief guest.",
                    "description": "In the simple past tense, the passive form is made with was/were + past participle form of the verb.",
                    "answers": [
                        "gave",
                        "were giving",
                        "were given"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "The child ……………………….. from drowning.",
                    "description": "In the simple past tense, the passive form is made with was/were + past participle form of the verb.",
                    "answers": [
                        "rescued",
                        "has rescued",
                        "was rescued"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "The match …………………………..",
                    "description": "In the present perfect, the passive form is made with has/have + been + ing form. ",
                    "answers": [
                        "has cancelled",
                        "has been cancelled",
                        "has been cancelling"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "The boy …………………………… to stand outside the class for an hour.",
                    "description": "In the simple past tense, the passive form is made with was/were + past participle form of the verb.",
                    "answers": [
                        "has made",
                        "was made",
                        "has been made"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "The man ……………………………. by a snake.",
                    "description": "In the simple past tense, the passive form is made with was/were + past participle form of the verb.",
                    "answers": [
                        "has bitten",
                        "was bitten",
                        "was biting"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "Dinner is ready …………………………….",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "to serve",
                        "to be served"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "Messengers ……………………….. to different parts of the country.",
                    "description": "In the simple past tense, the passive form is made with was/were + past participle form of the verb.",
                    "answers": [
                        "were sending",
                        "have sent",
                        "were sent"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "He ……………………………. for his alcoholic addiction.",
                    "description": "In the present continuous tense, the passive form is made with is/are/am + being + past participle form of the verb.",
                    "answers": [
                        "is treating",
                        "is being treated",
                        "has been treating"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "The boy ……………………………. with a cane.",
                    "description": "In the simple past tense, the passive form is made with was/were + past participle form of the verb.",
                    "answers": [
                        "was beating",
                        "has beaten",
                        "was beaten"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "The case ……………………………. by the police.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "is investigating",
                        "is been investigated",
                        "is being investigated"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "Hindi ………………………….. in much of North India.",
                    "description": "In the simple present tense, the passive form is made with is/am/are + past participle form of the verb.",
                    "answers": [
                        "is spoken",
                        "has spoken",
                        "is speaking"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "They …………………………. of the consequences.",
                    "description": "In the present perfect, the passive form is made with has/have + been + ing form. ",
                    "answers": [
                        "are warning",
                        "have been warned",
                        "have warned"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                }
            ]
        }
    ]
}